// questions that will be asked

{
    question: 'Where do the Weasleys go on holiday in the Prisoner of Azkaban?',
        choice1: 'France',
        choice2: 'Greece',
        choice3: 'Egypt',
        choice4: 'Romania',
    answer: 3,
},
{
    question: "What is the name of Hermione's cat?",
    answers: {
        choice: 'Errol',
        choice: 'Crookshanks',
        choice: 'Hedwig',
        choice: 'Scabbers',
    },
    correctAnswer: 2,
},
{
    question: "What do the dementors take when they kiss you?",
    answers: {
        choice: 'Magic ability',
        choice: 'Happiness',
        choice: 'Soul',
        choice: 'Life',
    },
    correctAnswer: 3,
},
{
    question: "What was the nickname of James Potter?",
    answers: {
        choice: 'Prongs',
        choice: 'Moony',
        choice: 'Wormtail',
        choice: 'Padfoot',
    },
    correctAnswer: 1,
},
{
    question: "What spell allows things to be concealed?",
    answers: {
        choice: 'Patronus Charm',
        choice: 'Fidelius Charm',
        choice: 'Caterwauling Charm',
        choice: 'Imperterbable Charm',
    },
    correctAnswer: 2,
},
{
    question: "Which teams played in the Quidditch World Cup?",
    answers: {
        choice: 'USA and Hungary',
        choice: 'France and Norway',
        choice: 'England and Romania',
        choice: 'Ireland and Bulgaria',
    },
    correctAnswer: 4,
},
{
    question: "What is the name of the magical school in France?",
    answers: {
        choice: 'Beauxbatons',
        choice: 'Durmstrang',
        choice: 'Ilvermorny',
        choice: 'Mahoutokoro',
    },
    correctAnswer: 1,
},
{
    question: "What does Harry Potter use in the second task in The Goblet of Fire?",
    answers: {
        choice: 'Confundus Charm',
        choice: 'Gillyweed',
        choice: 'Bubble-head Charm',
        choice: 'Transfiguration',
    },
    correctAnswer: 2,
},
{
    question: "What does Professor Binns teach?",
    answers: {
        choice: 'Charms',
        choice: 'Defense Against the Dark Arts',
        choice: 'A History of Magic',
        choice: 'Astronomy',
    },
    correctAnswer: 3,
},
{
    question: "Who is the cousin of Sirius Black?",
    answers: {
        choice: 'Voldemort',
        choice: 'Bellatrix Lestrange',
        choice: 'Lucius Malfoy',
        choice: 'Filius Flitwick',
    },
    correctAnswer: 2,
},
{
    question: "Who teaches Defence Against the Dark Arts in Order of the Phoenix?",
    answers: {
        choice: 'Remus Lupin',
        choice: 'Mad Eye Moody',
        choice: 'Severus Snape',
        choice: 'Dolores Umbridge',
    },
    correctAnswer: 4,
},
{
    question: "How many Horcruxes does Voldemort create?",
    answers: {
        choice: '5',
        choice: '6',
        choice: '7',
        choice: '8',
    },
    correctAnswer: 3,
},
{
    question: "Who owned Hepzibah Smiths cup with the badger on it?",
    answers: {
        choice: 'Helga Hufflepuff',
        choice: 'Borgin and Burke',
        choice: 'Grindewald',
        choice: 'Cornelius Fudge',
    },
    correctAnswer: 1,
},
{
    question: "Who discovers the original locket Horcrux?",
    answers: {
        choice: 'Albus Dumbledore',
        choice: 'Andromeda Tonks',
        choice: 'Regulus Black',
        choice: 'Tom Riddle',
    },
    correctAnswer: 3,
},
{
    question: "Who killed Nagini?",
    answers: {
        choice: 'Harry Potter',
        choice: 'Neville Longbottom',
        choice: 'Ginny Weasley',
        choice: 'Hermione Granger',
    },
    correctAnswer: 2,
},
{
    question: "What is the name of Remus Lupin's son?",
    answers: {
        choice: 'Albus',
        choice: 'Scorpius',
        choice: 'Hugo',
        choice: 'Teddy',
    },
    correctAnswer: 4,
},
];